A Guide to the Peter F. Geithner papers FA1408
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional and personal files, first run, 1963-2004; 1; 23.73 Cubic Feet About 57 LTR size Hollinger boxes, 1 Half-LTR size Hollinger box, and 4 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Strengthening Civil Society's Contribution to Development: The Role of Official Development Assistance, Report on a Conference Organized by the Overseas Development Council and the Synergos Institute, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Miscellaneous papers and articles regarding philanthropy, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Miscellaneous papers and articles regarding philanthropy, 1995-1998 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - European Foundation Centre (EFC) Members, Associations, and Networks, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - The Synergos Institute Voluntary Sector Financing Program - The Process and Techniques of Foundation-Building, Experiences from Eight Organisations in Africa, Asia, and Latin America, undated (Box 32, Folder 415-416)
  - CIVICUS World Alliance for Citizenship Participation - CIVICUS Asia Pacific Advisory Forum, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 417)
  - Research Report on Corporate Social Responsibility Project, PT Binaman Utama, 1995 August 31 (Box 32, Folder 418)
  - The New Civic Atlas: Profiles of Civil Society in 60 Countries, prepared for CIVICUS by Millennium Communications Group and Liza W. Poinier, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Legal Principles for Citizen Participation: Toward a Legal Framework for Civil Society, prepared for CIVICUS by International Center for Not-For-Profit Law (ICNL), 1997 (Box 32, Folder 420)
  - Building Civil Society Worldwide: Strategies for Successful Communications, prepared for CIVICUS by Millennium Communications Group and Liza W. Poinier, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 421)
  - European Foundation Centre (EFC) Rights and Benefits of Membership, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 422)
  - Asian NGO Coalition for Agrarian Reform and Rural Development (ANGOC) - Second Asia-Pacific Regional Meeting of the NGO Working Group of the World Bank, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 423)
  - The Asia Foundation Working Paper Series - Charities and Nonprofits in the U.S.: Regulation, Standard-Setting, Accreditation, and Monitoring, Russy D. Sumariwalla, 1998 January (Box 32, Folder 424)
  - Study of NGOs in Nine Asian Countries, prepared by Russell Rollason for International Development Support Services, 1998 March (Box 32, Folder 425)
  - U.S. Agency for International Development (USAID) Manila, Philippines - List of Registered Private Voluntary Organizations (PVOs)/Enterprise in Community Development (ECD) with USAID/Philippines, 1997 August 30 (Box 32, Folder 426)
  - Strengthening Civil Society: A Requisite for Good Governance and Sustainable Development presentation, undated (Box 32, Folder 427)
  - Evolution of a PVO Co-Financing Program: Lessons Learned at USAID/Philippines, Lynne Cripe and Gregory Perrier, 1997 May (Box 32, Folder 428)
  - Handbook on Good Practices for Laws Relating to Non-Governmental Organizations (Discussion Draft), prepared for the World Bank by the International Center for Not-for-Profit Law, 1997 May (Box 32, Folder 429)
  - Miscellaneous papers and reports regarding philanthropy, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 430)
  - Ford Foundation overview publication, circa 1994 (Box 33, Folder 431-432)
  - International Forum on Capacity Building (IFCB) publications, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 433-434)
  - Online Discussion of the World Bank's Comprehensive Development Framework (CDF), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 435)
  - Washington Center for Chinese Studies, 1996-1999 (Box 33, Folder 436)
  - United Nations Office for Project Services (UNOPS), 1999 (Box 33, Folder 437)
  - St. John's University, Shanghai, China, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 438)
  - The Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange (CUSCAE), 2000 (Box 33, Folder 439)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 440-442)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) Fiscal Year 2000 Annual Report, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 443)
  - Maureen and Mike Mansfield Foundation 1999-2000 Biennial Report, circa 2000 (Box 33, Folder 444)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Achieving Harmony in Trade and Environment grant project, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 445)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Government Transparency, Civil Society, and Democratic Institutions: American and Japanese Models for the Promotion of Informed Citizenry and Government Accountability in Asia grant project, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 446)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Conference and Email Discussion on Japanese Regional Relations, Security, and U.S.-Japan Relations grant project, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 447)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - U.S.-Japan Global Disclosure Policy Dialogue grant project, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 448)
  - Nautilus Institute for Security and Sustainable Development, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 449)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - The Search for Environmental Equity, Comparing the Roles of Japan, the U.S., Germany, and the European Union, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 450)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - The Team Approach in Japan and the U.S.: Where Are We Now and Where Should We Be in the Future?, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 451)
  - University of Michigan 2001 Financial Report, circa 2001 (Box 34, Folder 452)
  - Miscellaneous papers and articles regarding economic and social change in China, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 453)
  - Pamphlets regarding U.S.-China foreign relations, 1998-2001 (Box 34, Folder 454)
  - Miscellaneous papers and reports regarding economic development and regional security in Asia, 1994-2002 (Box 34, Folder 455)
  - Asia Foundation - Legal reform and World Trade Organization (WTO) compliance in China, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 456)
  - Committee on Legal Education Exchange with China (CLEEC) evaluation draft, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 457)
  - Asian Development Bank (ADB) Newsletters, 2002 May (Box 34, Folder 458)
  - Summary of the National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP) Trip to Beijing, Shanghai, and Taipei, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 459)
  - The Military Component of the U.S.-People's Republic of China (PRC) Relationship, Alfred D. Wilhelm Jr., 2001 (Box 34, Folder 460)
  - Ballistic Missile Defense and Northeast Asia Security: Views from Washington, Beijing, and Tokyo, Evan S. Medeiros, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 461)
  - Taiwan Security Research - Major Events in Sino-U.S. Ties, 2002 April (Box 34, Folder 462)
  - The Conference Board - Restructuring Chinese Enterprises: The Effects of Federalism and Privatization Initiatives on Business Performance, Robert H. McGuckin an Sean M. Doughtery, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 463)
  - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (NCAFP) Roundtable, Co-sponsored with the Institute of Taiwan Studies, Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, Beijing, on U.S.-China Relations and the Taiwan Issue, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 464)
  - Hu Jintao speech - Enhanced Mutual Understanding and Trust Towards a Constructive and Cooperative Relationship Between China and the U.S., 2002 (Box 34, Folder 465)
  - Under Secretary of Defense (Policy) 1999 Summer Study Final Report: Asia 2025, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 466-467)
  - Asian Affairs: An American Review, Vol. 28, No. 3, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Human Rights in China (HRIC), 2001 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Towards an East Asian Community: Region of Peace, Prosperity, and Progress - East Asia Vision Group Report, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 470)
  - International Symposium on "Sino-U.S. Relations in Retrospect and Prospect" Summary, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 471)
  - The Nixon Center - A Big Power Agenda for East Asia: America, China, and Japan, David M. Lampton and Gregory C. May, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 472)
  - Exceptional Resources Group (ERG) - Short Report on Wilton Park Conference 621: China and Her Neighbours, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 473)
  - Asian Perspective, Vol. 25, No. 1 - Taiwan at a Crossroads, Sheng Lijun, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 474)
  - Miscellaneous papers regarding China and U.S.-China relations, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 475)
  - Miscellaneous journal publications regarding Asia and U.S.-Asia relations, 1999-2001 (Box 35, Folder 476)
  - Miscellaneous papers and articles regarding China and U.S.-Asia relations, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 477-478)
  - National Committee reports regarding U.S.-China relations, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 479)
  - Miscellaneous papers and reports regarding China and China-U.S. relations, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Seminars regarding China and U.S.-China relations, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - America's Role in Asia: Asian Views, Tadashi Yamamoto, Pranee Thiparat, and Abdul Ahsan, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - America's Asian Alliances, edited by Robert D. Blackwill and Paul Dibb, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Social Protection in Asia: Addressing Exclusion, Challenging Orthodoxy, prepared for the Ford Foundation, undated (Box 35, Folder 484-485)
  - Miscellaneous papers and articles regarding Asia and U.S.-China relations, 1996-2001 (Box 36, Folder 486)
  - Harvard University journal publications regarding Asia, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 487)
  - Miscellaneous reports and articles regarding U.S.-China relations, 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 488)
  - The Nixon Center - Managing U.S.-China Relations in the Twenty-First Century. David M. Lampton and Gregory C. May, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 489)
  - Miscellaneous reports and articles regarding China and U.S.-China relations, 1996-2002 (Box 36, Folder 490)
  - Exceptional Resources Group (ERG) - China Beyond Fifty, circa 1999 (Box 36, Folder 491)
  - Pamphlets and brochures regarding philanthropy in India and the Ford Foundation in India, 2000-2002 (Box 36, Folder 492)
  - Ford Foundation New Delhi, India Office and Indian foundations, 1996-2002 (Box 36, Folder 493-494)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 495-498)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Disenfranchisement: Civil Society and Participation in International Environmental Governance grant project, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 499-500)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Managing Nuclear Proliferation in the Middle East and South Asia: Implications for the Nuclear Nonproliferation Regime grant project, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 501)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Alliance for Engagement: Building Cooperation in Security Relations with China grant project, 1994-2002 (Box 37, Folder 502)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Patriotism, Power, and the Legacies of War: Redefining Japan's Role in the World grant project, 2001-2002 (Box 37, Folder 503)
  - Pacific Forum Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) - Programs and Special Activities, 2002 January (Box 37, Folder 504)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) as a Bridge Between East Asia and Latin America and Evaluating APEC Institutional Reforms grant project, 1993-2002 (Box 37, Folder 505)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Navigating Peace: Forging New Water Partnerships grant project, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 506)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 507)
  - Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) consultancy appointment - Asia Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 508)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 509-510)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 1985-2001 (Box 38, Folder 511-513)
  - Ford Foundation - International Relations Studies in China Today: Achievements, Trends and Conditions, 2001 August (Box 38, Folder 514)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 515)
  - Stanley Foundation publications, 2000-2001 (Box 38, Folder 516)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 1979-2001 (Box 39, Folder 517-520)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment - List of China grants, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 521-523)
  - World Economics and Politics - Contents pages, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 524)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment - 1996-2000 Fiscal Years' grant commitments for China, 1996-2001 (Box 39, Folder 525)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 526)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment - Shanghai, China, 1997-2001 (Box 39, Folder 527-528)
  - Ford Foundation Beijing, China Office consultancy appointment, 1991-2001 (Box 40, Folder 529)
  - Asia Foundation 2001 Annual Report, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 530)
  - Institute of Defense and Strategic Studies (IDSS) Working Paper No. 12 - Globalization and its Implications for Southeast Asian Security: A Vietnamese Perspective, 2001 May (Box 40, Folder 531)
  - National Center for Social Sciences and Humanities of Vietnam (NCSSH), 2000 (Box 40, Folder 532)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 1975-2002 (Box 40, Folder 533-535)
  - Program for International Studies in Asia (PISA) - Reports on meeting on Curriculum and Program Development in International Affairs, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 536)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 1981-2002; File contains an unlabeled CD (folder 540). (Box 40, Folder 537-540)
  - Untitled CD (Box 40, Folder 540)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 2000-2001 (Box 40, Folder 541)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 542)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 1997-2002 (Box 41, Folder 543-546)
  - Ford Foundation Hanoi, Vietnam Office consultancy appointment, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 547-548)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Project on New Institutionalism in Asia, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 549-550)
  - Policy documents regarding U.S.-China relations, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 551)
  - HSBC Economics Forum - Reform and Development of China's Financial System, Peter Bottelier, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 552)
  - Peaceworks No. 44 - Democratic Values, Political Structures, and Alternative Politics in Greater China, David Zweig, 2002 July (Box 41, Folder 553)
  - The Yale-China Health Journal, Vol. 1, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 554)
  - The India-China Relationship: What the United States Needs to Know Conference Report, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 555)
  - Harvard China Review, Vol. 3, No. 2 - Toward Better Education in China, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 556)
  - The Aspen Institute Congressional Program Conference on U.S.-China Relations report, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 557)
  - Miscellaneous reports and journal publications regarding China and U.S.-China relations, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 558-559)
  - Promotional material for Asia-centered and Chinese-American philanthropy, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 560)
  - Committee of 100 Annual Conference - Seeking Common Ground, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 561)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government - Research papers, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 562)
  - Stephen Denney forwarded email - State's attention to overseas Vietnamese, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 563)
  - Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations website, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 564)
  - Committee of 100, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 565-566)
  - American Indian Foundation (AIF) 2001-2002 Annual Report (Box 42, Folder 567)
  - American Indian Foundation (AIF), 2002 (Box 42, Folder 568)
  - American Indian Foundation (AIF), 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 569)
  - American Indian Foundation (AIF) Quarterly Newsletter - Fourth Quarter, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 570)
  - American Indian Foundation (AIF), 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 571)
  - Diaspora philanthropy articles in Chronicle of Philanthropy, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 572)
  - Background related to Mark's paper, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 573)
  - Website pages for foundations in India and South Asia, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 574)
  - Philanthropy development in the Asia-Pacific and diaspora philanthropy, 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 575-576)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) background paper, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 577)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002 (Box 43, Folder 578)
  - U.S. Department of the Treasury anti-terrorism regulations, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 579)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Joanna Handlin Smith, 1987-2002 (Box 43, Folder 580)
  - Manas website pages, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 581)
  - Indian diaspora and Indian diaspora philanthropy, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 582)
  - IndianNGOs webpages, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 583)
  - The Foreign Exchange of Hate: The India Development and Relief Fund (IDRF) and the American Funding of Hindutva, Sabrang Communications, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 584)
  - Miscellaneous papers and reports regarding diaspora philanthropy, 1997-2003 (Box 43, Folder 585)
  - Marion R. Fremont-Smith papers regarding government regulation of philanthropic organizations, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 586)
  - Diasporas and diaspora philanthropy, 2000-2003 (Box 43, Folder 587)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 588)
  - Website pages for philanthropic and advocacy organizations, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 589)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center for the Study of Philanthropy - Topics in Asian American Philanthropy and Voluntarism, an Extension Course Guide, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 590)
  - New India-Times articles, 2003 January 24 (Box 44, Folder 591)
  - Business Week - The New Face of Philanthropy, 2002 December 2 (Box 44, Folder 592)
  - Possible connections between Indian diaspora philanthropy and hate groups in India, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 593)
  - India Abroad - What does Mr. Agnihotri mean by 'freedom'?, Vijay Prashad, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 594)
  - Goldsea Asian American Demographics - Parsing Asian America, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 595)
  - AnnaLee Saxenian biography, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 596)
  - Vinay Lal biography, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 597)
  - LexisNexis Academic articles regarding the Indian diaspora and Indian diaspora philanthropy, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 598)
  - Miscellaneous articles regarding diasporas and emigration, 2002 November (Box 44, Folder 599)
  - China - Legislation on foundations, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 600)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) The Center for the Study of Philanthropy letter, 2002 December 10 (Box 44, Folder 601)
  - Charities Aid Foundation India (CAF) - Seminar on Mapping and Discussing Non-Resident Indian (NRI) Philanthropy, Vol. I, circa 2000 (Box 44, Folder 602)
  - Charities Aid Foundation India (CAF) - Seminar on Mapping and Discussing Non-Resident Indian (NRI) Philanthropy, Vol. 2, circa 2000 (Box 44, Folder 603)
  - Cross-border Philanthropy: An Exploratory Study of International Giving in the U.K., the U.S., Germany and Japan, edited by Helmut K. Anheier and Regina List, undated (Box 44, Folder 604)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center for the Study of Philanthropy - Philanthropy Among Middle Eastern Americans and Their Historical Traditions of Giving, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 605)
  - Israeli Center for Third Sector Research publications, 2000-2002 (Box 44, Folder 606-607)
  - Association for Research on Nonprofit Organizations and Voluntary Action (ARNOVA) Occasional Paper Series - Vol. 1, No. 1 - Philanthropy in Communities of Color: Traditions and Challenges, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 608)
  - New York Times - A Special Section: Giving, 2002 November 18 (Box 44, Folder 609)
  - Public Policy Institute of California (PPIC) - Local and Global Networks of Immigrant Professionals in Silicon Valley, AnnaLee Saxenian with Yasuyuki Motoyama and Xiaohong Quan, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 610)
  - India Review, Vol. 1, No. 2, 2002 April (Box 45, Folder 611)
  - Charities Aid Foundation India (CAF) - Indian Diaspora and Giving Patterns of Indian Americans in U.S.A., edited by R. Gopa Kumar, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 612)
  - India's Missed Opportunity: India's Relationship with the Non Resident Indians, M. C. Lall, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 613)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Funding, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 614-615)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Discussants, paid, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 616)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Paper writers, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 617)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Invitees, unpaid, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 618-619)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Diaspora philanthropists, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 620-621)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW) - Agenda, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 622)
  - Neelan Tiruchelvam Commemoration Programme, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 623-625)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) - Future plans, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 626)
  - Asian Development Research Forum (ADRF) Annual Conference - Asian Transition: ADRF and a New Challenge, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 627-630)
  - Mark Sidel papers and reports regarding philanthropy and law, 2001-2003 (Box 47, Folder 631)
  - Diaspora: The New Philanthropy?, Esther Lethlean, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 632)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Global Philanthropy, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 633)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Original Rockefeller Foundation Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 634)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI), 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 635)
  - Human security, 2000-2002 (Box 47, Folder 636-637)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Global Philanthropy, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 638)
  - Flexner 21, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 639)
  - Investing in People: Leadership for Global Health, Lincoln Chen, 2001 February 16 (Box 47, Folder 640)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 641-643)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 644)
  - Jagat S. Mehta address and article, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 645)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002 (Box 48, Folder 646)
  - Indian American Alliance Venture Fund, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 647)
  - Craig Smith paper proposal, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 648)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Philanthropy and Education, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 649)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 650)
  - Council on Foreign Relations meeting - Business with a Social Agenda - Good for Society?: "Corporate Social Responsibility" and the Globalization Debate, 2002 February 5 (Box 48, Folder 651)
  - Mark Sidel papers and reports regarding philanthropy and law, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 652)
  - Global Giving Matters Newsletter, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 653)
  - Centre for Policy Research - Ethnicity and International Relations at the Turn of the Century: Policy Perspectives for India, Jagat S. Mehta, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 654)
  - Harvard University Diaspora Philanthropy Workshop (DPW), 2002 (Box 48, Folder 655)